George Korson Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscripts
  - Subseries E: Manuscripts of published works
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (26 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (27 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (28 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - At his side: the story of the American Red cross overseas in World War II, circa 1945 (Box-folder 37/7)
      Published by Coward-McCann in 1945.
    - The child's book of folklore: book plan, circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/1)
      Published by Dial Press in 1947.
    - The child's book of folklore: draft, circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/2)
      See note for box-folder 38/1.
    - The child's book of folklore: publicity, circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - The child's book of folklore: research materials (1 of 4), circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - The child's book of folklore: research materials (2 of 4), circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - The child's book of folklore: research materials (3 of 4), circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - The child's book of folklore: research materials (4 of 4), circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Songs and ballads of the anthracite miners (sound recording), circa 1947 (Box-folder 38/8)
      First released by the Library of Congress in 1947.
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: book proposal, circa 1949 (Box-folder 38/9)
      Published by the University of Pennsylvania Press in 1949.
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: contract, circa 1949 (Box-folder 38/10)
      See note for box-folder 38/9.
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: editorial instructions, circa 1949 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("British folk tradition" - S.P. Bayard) (1 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("British folk tradition" - S.P. Bayard) (2 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Pennsylvania German songs" - Brendle, Troxell) (1 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Pennsylvania German songs" - Brendle, Troxell) (2 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Amish hymns as folk music" - J.W. Frey), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Cornplanter Indians" - M. Deardorff), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Central Pennsylvania legends" - H.W. Shoemaker), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Pike County tall tales" - Robert J. Wheeler), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Conestoga wagoners" - H.C. Frey), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Canallers" - Lewis E. Theiss), circa 1949 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Railroaders" - Freeman Hubbard), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Lumberjacks and raftsmen" - J. Walker) (1 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Lumberjacks and raftsmen" - J. Walker) (2 of 2), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("The coal miners" - George Korson), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Folk songs of an industrial city" - Jacob Evanson) (1 of 4), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Folk songs of an industrial city" - Jacob Evanson) (2 of 4), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Folk songs of an industrial city" - Jacob Evanson) (3 of 4), circa 1949 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: draft ("Folk songs of an industrial city" - Jacob Evanson) (4 of 4), circa 1949 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: galleys, circa 1949 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: publicity, circa 1949 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: miscellaneous materials, circa 1949 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Black rock: mining folklore of the Pennsylvania Dutch: application for Guggenheim grant, 1957 (Box-folder 41/5)
      First published by Johns Hopkins Press, 1960. The page proofs for the book have been relocated to box-folder 94/14.
    - Black rock: application for renewal of Guggenheim grant, 1958 (Box-folder 41/6)
      See note for box-folder 41/5.
    - Black rock: book outline, circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 1 (chapters 1-10) (1 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 1 (chapters 1-10) (2 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 1 (chapters 11-20; source notes) (1 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 1 (chapters 11-20; source notes) (2 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 2 (preface, chapters 1-10) (1 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 2 (preface, chapters 1-10) (2 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 2 (chapters 11-20, source notes, index) (1 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 2 (chapters 11-20, source notes, index) (2 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Black rock: manuscript, part 2 (chapters 11-20, source notes, index) (3 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Black rock: song texts and music, chapters 18 and 20, circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Black rock: miscellaneous revisions (1 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Black rock: miscellaneous revisions (2 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Black rock: miscellaneous revisions (3 of 3), circa 1960 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Black rock: illustrations, chapters 1-10, circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Black rock: illustrations, chapters 11-20, circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Black rock: illustrations, circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Black rock: galleys (1 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Black rock: galleys (2 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Black rock: publicity, circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Black rock: research notes (texts and tunes), circa 1960 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Black rock: research notes (documents) (1 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Black rock: research notes (documents) (2 of 2), circa 1960 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Black rock: research notes (1 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Black rock: research notes (2 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Black rock: research notes (3 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Black rock: research notes (4 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Black rock: research notes (5 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Black rock: research notes (6 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - Black rock: research notes (7 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - Black rock: research notes (8 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Black rock: research notes (9 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - Black rock: research notes (10 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Black rock: research notes (11 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 47/3)
    - Black rock: research notes (12 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - Black rock: research notes (13 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Black rock: research notes (14 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Black rock: research notes (15 of 15), circa 1960 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Songs and ballads of the bituminous miners (sound recording): draft (manuscript of accompanying pamphlet) (1 of 2), circa 1965 (Box-folder 48/4)
      First released by the Library of Congress in 1965.
    - Songs and ballads of the bituminous miners (sound recording): draft (manuscript of accompanying pamphlet) (2 of 2), circa 1965 (Box-folder 48/5)
      See note for box-folder 48/4.
    - Songs and ballads of the bituminous miners (sound recording): publicity and miscellaneous (1 of 2), circa 1965 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Songs and ballads of the bituminous miners (sound recording): publicity and miscellaneous (2 of 2), circa 1965 (Box-folder 49/1)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: editorial instructions, circa 1970 (Box-folder 49/2)
      Published by Bobbs-Merrill in 1970.
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: tentative outline, chapters 4-15, circa 1970 (Box-folder 49/3)
      See note for box-folder 49/2.
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript), chapters 1-5, circa 1970 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript), chapters 6, unidentified, circa 1970 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript) (1 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript) (2 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript) (3 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript) (4 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (manuscript) (5 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: draft (complete manuscript), circa 1970 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: research material (1 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: research material (2 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: research material (3 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: research material (4 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: research material (5 of 5), circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: publicity, circa 1970 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - "The coal miners" ( Regional American Folklore manuscript) (Box-folder 51/7)
  - Subseries F: Unpublished materials
    - "Industrial folklore" ( Encyclopedia of labor manuscript) (Box-folder 52/1)
    - "Molly Maguires" ( Encyclopedia of labor manuscript) (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Miscellaneous material ( Encyclopedia of labor manuscripts) (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Folk heroes are only human: book plan (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Folk heroes are only human: miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Folk heroes are only human: miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Folk heroes are only human: map (Box-folder 52/7)
    - The itinerant peddler: book proposal (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Miracle metals: prospectus (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Sorensen: contract (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Sorensen: manuscript (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Sorensen: research materials (1 of 2) (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Sorensen: research materials (2 of 2) (Box-folder 53/6)
  - Subseries G: Fieldnotes
    - Anthracite folk songs and folklore (1 of 4), 1931 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Anthracite folk songs and folklore (2 of 4), 1931 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Anthracite folk songs and folklore (3 of 4), 1931 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Anthracite folk songs and folklore (4 of 4), 1931 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Bituminous folk songs and folklore, southern Appalachia (1 of 2), 1940 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Bituminous folk songs and folklore, southern Appalachia (2 of 2), 1940 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Pennsylvania Dutch/anthracite folk songs and folklore (1 of 2), circa 1957 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - Pennsylvania Dutch/anthracite folk songs and folklore (2 of 2), circa 1957 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Subseries H: Song texts and tunes
    Undated manuscripts.
    - Song texts and tunes: A (1 of 2) (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Song texts and tunes: A (2 of 2) (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Song texts and tunes: B (1 of 3) (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Song texts and tunes: B (2 of 3) (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Song texts and tunes: B (3 of 3) (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Song texts and tunes: C (1 of 2) (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Song texts and tunes: C (2 of 2) (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Song texts and tunes: D (1 of 3) (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Song texts and tunes: D (2 of 3) (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Song texts and tunes: D (3 of 3) (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Song texts and tunes: E (Box-folder 55/12)
    - Song texts and tunes: F (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Song texts and tunes: G (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Song texts and tunes: H (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Song texts and tunes: I (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Song texts and tunes: J (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Song texts and tunes: K (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Song texts and tunes: L (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Song texts and tunes: M (1 of 4) (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Song texts and tunes: M (2 of 4) (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Song texts and tunes: M (3 of 4) (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Song texts and tunes: M (4 of 4) (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Song texts and tunes: N (Box-folder 56/12)
    - Song texts and tunes: O (1 of 2) (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Song texts and tunes: O (2 of 2) (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Song texts and tunes: P (1 of 2) (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Song texts and tunes: P (2 of 2) (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Song texts and tunes: R (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Song texts and tunes: S (1 of 4) (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Song texts and tunes: S (2 of 4) (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Song texts and tunes: S (3 of 4) (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Song texts and tunes: S (4 of 4) (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Song texts and tunes: T (1 of 3) (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Song texts and tunes: T (2 of 3) (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Song texts and tunes: T (3 of 3) (Box-folder 57/10)
    - Song texts and tunes: U (Box-folder 57/11)
    - Song texts and tunes: W (1 of 3) (Box-folder 57/12)
    - Song texts and tunes: W (2 of 3) (Box-folder 57/13)
    - Song texts and tunes: W (3 of 3) (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Song texts and tunes: Y (Box-folder 57/15)
    - Song texts and tunes: general (1 of 3) (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Song texts and tunes: general (2 of 3) (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Song texts and tunes: general (3 of 3) (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Song texts and tunes: general (index cards) (Box-folder 58/4)
  - Subseries I: Folk festivals
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1935 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1936: plans and participants (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1936: administrative committee minutes (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1936: expenses (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1936: publicity (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1937: plans (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1937: administrative committee minutes (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1937: expenses (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1937: publicity (Box-folder 58/13)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1938 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1949: plans and participants (Box-folder 58/15)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1949: expenses (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, 1949: publicity (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival: miscellaneous (Box-folder 59/3)
    - National Folk Festival: programs, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - National Folk Festival: publicity (1 of 2), circa 1935-1954 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - National Folk Festival: publicity (2 of 2), circa 1935-1954 (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Subseries J: Clippings
    - Songs and ballads of the anthracite miners: reviews (photocopies) (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: reviews (photocopies) (Box-folder 59/8)
      See Box 87.
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: reviews (photocopies) (Box-folder 59/9)
      See Box 88.
    - At his side: reviews (photocopies) (Box-folder 59/10)
      See Box 89.
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, December 1948-June 1949 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, July 1949 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, August 1949 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, September 1949 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, October 1949-December 1949 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Pennsylvania songs and legends: reviews, March 1950-March 1961 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Black rock: reviews (1 of 2), circa 1941 (Box-folder 60/7)
      See Box 90.
    - Black rock: reviews (2 of 2), circa 1941 (Box-folder 60/8)
      See note for box-folder 60/7.
    - Black land: reviews, circa 1941 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - The child's book of folklore: reviews, August 1947-October 1948 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - John L. Lewis: young militant labor leader: reviews (Box-folder 60/11)
    - The miner sings: reviews, January-May 1938 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Pennsylvania folk songs and ballads: reviews (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Songs and ballads of the anthracite miners: reviews, January 1946-June 1965 (Box-folder 60/14)
      See Box 86.
    - Songs and ballads of the bituminous miners: reviews, December 1964-February 1967 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - George Korson: clippings, 1935-1949 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - George Korson: clippings, 1950-1957 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - George Korson: clippings, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - George Korson: clippings, circa 1965-1971 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - George Korson: obituaries (photocopies), circa 1967 (Box-folder 61/5)
      See Box 93.
    - First annual Pennsylvania Folk Festival, Allentown (photocopies), 1935 (Box-folder 61/6)
      See Box 83.
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival (1 of 4), 1936 (Box-folder 61/7)
      Photocopies. See Boxes 84 and 85.
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival (2 of 4), 1936 (Box-folder 61/8)
      Photocopies. See note for box-folder 6/7.
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival (3 of 4), 1936 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival (4 of 4), 1936 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, April-September 1937 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, February-June 1938 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, October-November 1949; undated (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Beliefs, customs, and superstitions, July 1931-July 1971 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Coal mine disasters, July 1931-August 1940 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Coal mine disasters, July 1941-July 1971 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Coal mine disasters, undated (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1874-1880 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1922-1926 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Coal miners and mining, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Coal miners and mining, undated (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Folk art, 1936-1966 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Ethnic groups, 1932-1968 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Folk art: coal carving, 1914-1970 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Folk festivals, 1935-1963 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - Folk heroes, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Folk language, 1939-1962 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Folk medicine, 1953-1956; undated (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Folk song, October 1927-April 1957 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Folk song, undated (Box-folder 64/8)
    - Folktales, 1947-1953; undated (Box-folder 64/9)
    - Gravity railroad, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - John L. Lewis, 1935-1962 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - John L. Lewis, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - Lumber, 1936-1966; undated (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936-1965 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Molly Maguires, 1919-1965 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Molly Maguires, June 1951-December 1952 (Box-folder 65/5)
      A series by James Corrigan in Anthracite Tri District News.
    - Mules, rats, etc., 1931-1941 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Pennsylvania, 1931-1959 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Pennsylvania, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Pennsylvania: Hazleton Plain Speaker (historical series), 1932 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Pennsylvania: Herzog, Walter. "Recollections of a Shamokin boy." Shamokin Citizen, 1955 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Pennsylvania: Kreamer, Ralph. "Carbon County panorama." Allentown Sunday Call Chronicle, July 1954-1959 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Pennsylvania: Shoemaker, Henry W. "This morning's comment." Altoona Tribune, July 1934-January 1950 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Pennsylvania: Wheeler, Robert. "Pike County tall tales," undated (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Pennsylvania Folklore Society, April 1957-December 1958 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Pennsylvania Germans, undated (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Personalities, A-K (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Personalities, L-W (Box-folder 67/2)
  - Subseries K: Miscellany
    - Notebooks (1 of 4) (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Notebooks (2 of 4) (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Notebooks (3 of 4) (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Notebooks (4 of 4) (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Research material (1 of 3) (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Research material (2 of 3) (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Research material (3 of 3) (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Research, drafts, etc. (1 of 2) (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Research, drafts, etc. (2 of 2) (Box-folder 68/4)
    - Mailing lists (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Names, addresses, etc. (1 of 2) (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Names, addresses, etc. (2 of 2) (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Manuscript materials from photograph folders (Box-folder 68/8)
      Two items received with photographs, not associated with any particular one or group.
  - Subseries L: Audio tape transcripts and song logs
    Typewritten transcripts for audio tapes, created after the collection inventory was published. There is no tape or transcript for AFC 2003/011: SR077. Some typographical errors appear in the transcripts, especially for names. Unless otherwise identified, all recordings were made by George Korson. See Series 2 for further details.
    - AFC 2003/011: SR001 (transcripts), July 14, 1957 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR002 (part 1) (transcript), July 15, 1957 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR002 (part 2) (transcript), June 29, 1958 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR003 (transcripts), July 17, 1957 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR004 (transcripts), July 17, 1957 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR005 (transcript), July 17, 1957 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR006 (transcript), July 19, 1957 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR007 (transcript), July 19, 1957 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR008 (transcripts), July 21, 1957 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR009 (transcript), July 25, 1957 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR010 (transcript), July 25, 1957 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR011 (transcript), July 31, 1957 (Box-folder 69/12)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR012 (transcript), August 1, 1957 (Box-folder 69/13)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR013 (transcript), August 2, 1957 (Box-folder 69/14)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR014 (transcripts), August 2, 1957 (Box-folder 69/15)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR015 (transcripts), August 3, 1957; August 12, 1957 (Box-folder 69/16)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR016 (transcripts), August 15, 1957 (Box-folder 69/17)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR017 (transcript), August 6, 1957 (Box-folder 69/18)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR018 (transcripts), August 5, 1957; August 7, 1957 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - AFC 2003/011: SR019 (transcript), August 7, 1957 (Box-folder 70/2)